I'm going to go out on a high note.
600,000.
Another youngster.
Let's do a temporary fix first.
Wait a minute, this is bad.
An-go an-go!
Hello, I'm Akari Nibun of Hinatazaka 46.
Today I'm here in Akihabara.
A street with an Akihabara feel
This time, I came here to build my own PC.
I've been longing for a home-built PC for a long time now.
I've always wanted to make a home-built PC.
Akihabara is not Akihabara
There are a lot of stores selling PC parts and so on.
I want to go there.
to buy a home-built PC.
I have to buy the parts one by one by myself.
I have to buy the case and so on.
Windows OS
Motherboard, etc.
I need a lot of different parts.
It's the first time for me, isn't it?
This is the first time for me to build a computer from scratch.
I'm looking forward to it!
I come to Akihabara more often than I thought I would.
There are a lot of restaurants.
It's a battleground.
Oh, no, I'm here when I talked about restaurants!
Ta-da!
We've arrived at Tsukumo-san!
I'm going to choose parts and build my own PC here!
Mr. Kamioka, who will help me choose parts for my home-built PC today and teach me how to build it.
Mr. Kamioka, who will help us to choose the parts for our home-built PC today, and teach us how to build it.
Mr. Kamioka, who will teach us how to build our own PC.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, please let me film you.
Please allow me to show you.
Please let me see it.
If you don't mind, I'd like to take a look at the outer PC case.
From the case?
Yes, sir.
If you would like to take a look.
PC case corner
Wow, there are so many!
They are so big!
I was thinking of going with a black base this time.
It's so cool!
I want to make a cool gaming PC.
I want to make it.
But I'd like a case with glass walls so I can see what's inside.
Pillarless cases with glass on the sides are very popular these days.
Is that a trend?
I'm thinking of making it double-sided.
This one is really shiny right now.
This shiny part is not a case, is it?
No, it's already there from the beginning.
Oh, there's a shiny part on the case?
Is there a shiny part on the case?
Yes, it is.
Yes, sir.
That's cool.
Yes, it is.
Oh, it's kinda cool.
I'm going to go with "cool.
So is there anything that's a little bit difficult to clean?
It's glass, so here...
Loosen it up.
I'll just wipe the air out of the inside.
Oh, I'm just gonna make it look really cool.
This way, okay? I think I'm going to go ahead and do it.
I'd like to do it this way.
It's a great case.
Can I go with this one in black?
Yes, this one, please.
Yes, sir.
Yes, please.
We've decided on the case.
Great, great, great case!
Shut up.
Now, I'd like to choose a video card.
What do you mean by "video card"?
G-Force or something like that?
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
It's the most important part of the game.
You have 90? 4090?
This is the newest one.
I'm using a 2080 right now.
No, no, no, no.
No, I don't think so.
But it's nice of you to use it.
Thank you very much.
I bought it in about 2020.
I bought a very nice one back then...
Wait a minute.
600,000.
Really?
Really.
You can buy another computer.
Yes, sir.
How about a screen?
I'm on a bit of a budget. What do you recommend?
I recommend the PNY.
The one with three fans?
It glows.
Oh, it's so cool!
Then I'd like this one with three glowing fans.
This one, please. Thank you.
They're the ones at the bottom of the line. They're on sale today at the PNY Super Shop.
PNY Super Shop is out today. It's out today?
It's like a higher-end version of the one I'm choosing now.
Wait a minute.
I'm just a girl who's attracted to the newest model that's on sale today.
Should I switch to this newest model that's on sale today?
No problem at all.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm sorry. No problem.
Excuse me.
I dropped it because I borrowed it.
I'd like to use this one, which is on sale today.
I'll have this ready for you.
We've decided on something pretty big, haven't we?
Yes, it's the most important part of the game.
I've already made a decision.
Next is the most important part of the computer, the CPU.
The motherboard for the CPU and video card.
Motherboard
The one I'm going to recommend this time is
Intel Core i series.
Besides gaming, how about video editing?
Editing...I have a separate computer for editing.
I have a separate Mac computer for editing.
But to be honest, it's really hard to project.
I'd like to be able to use one computer in the future.
In that case, it would be great if you could install this.
If you install it, you can play games and distribute at the same time.
I can also edit videos while playing games and distributing them.
Yes, I think I can explain it in a simple way.
Then, what do you recommend?
Next is the motherboard.
Yes, motherboards.
It can be black or white.
There are many kinds of motherboards in terms of performance and expandability.
There are many kinds of motherboards.
This is the one I was going to show you this time.
Wow!
It's made by a manufacturer called ASUS.
Warlord for 18 consecutive years
It's not a warlord, but...
It's a durable model for people who play games.
So it can be used for many years?
Yes, that's right.
Even if you put the maximum load on the CPA you chose this time
Even if you put maximum load on it
It's made to be durable enough to withstand the maximum load.
Even if you max it out?
Yes, we do.
I believe you.
I'll take this one.
Thank you very much.
Next is the CPU cooler to cool the CPU.
Cooler.
Now, there are two main types of coolers, one is for cooling the CPU with water.
This simple water-cooling type
Air cooler
There are two types of air coolers.
In order to put it in the case this time, I used simple water cooling.
Make it shiny and bright!
It's even cooler!
The cooling capacity is higher than air cooling.
It's more expensive than air cooling.
So it's expensive.
Yes, it is.
The price range is pretty wide.
Are the temperatures displayed differently?
Of course, it's possible to display numbers and such here.
It's got a little fan or something like that.
There's also a small fan.
memory around the CPU and so on.
It's a system that blows air around the CPU
It's a system that can blow air around the CPU and the memory.
If you choose this type of case
As you can see, there are a lot of fans.
It's true that the case has a lot of fans.
The fan of the case will cool the case.
The fan itself cools the case, right?
That's right.
Then it's going to be full of fans.
I'd like to use only those that display the temperature.
Grown-up shopping.
Some memory also glows.
Memory glows.
It's glowing vertically.
That's it, right?
Yes, it is.
It's so cool.
I'd like to make it glow.
There's a popular and well-selling one over here called "Scheigh Mix.
Does it seem relatively fast?
I think it's pretty fast.
Pretty fast?
Then I want it to be very fast.
If you want to have enough power supply for the video card and CPU.
I'm thinking 850W or so.
850 watts.
Okay, I'll go with the 150.
Let's go with the 850.
Okay.
For normal usage.
I will suggest this one here on this Windows 11 home
Yes, sir
So, in order for me to build my own PC this time
I bought the parts here.
I found it.
It's all here.
This is going to be a PC.
I'll do my best to make it.
Thank you for choosing with us.
Yes, sir.
Now, let's start assembling.
I'd like you to help us, or rather, teach us.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Ito, you'll start with the motherboard, right?
Motherboard and CPU.
CPU
CPU. CPU.
I'm sorry.
Wow, it's so spiky!
Wow, it's spiky.
It's a computer part.
Wow, this kind of thing makes me nervous.
I love to assemble things.
I love shelves and moving screws.
I'm confident I can do that.
I'm confident I can do that, but this is pretty detailed.
Open here.
Really?
I'm sure it'll open... without removing it.
You can push the lever in and out.
It's a little more sexy than the other way around.
Wow!
This is a core iron.
Excuse me.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm a complete novice! Yes, with my back to the right, facing this way.
I'm so nervous.
I'm in.
There's a triangle here. Now close it.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Now, press the lever.
So this black lid comes off automatically.
Wow, you put a lot of force into this.
And then, this lid...
Installation is completed.
CPU
Next, let's install the SSD
Wow, this is also very delicate
Oh, this way
Wow!
The shape of the screws...
I don't see much.
I don't think so.
Maybe it's off.
Give me the other one.
Yes, sir.
Forever. Is it off?
Oh, it's off. Now, I'll have you insert it here, here, and this part will move and lock in place.
I see.
Here it comes.
And lock it.
Yes, I've got it!
SSD attached!
I'd like to attach the memory here
It's only supposed to stick when it sticks.
I think it's this way...
It's the other way.
It was the other way!
This way...
It's stuck.
I'm done sticking in the memory.
It's going pretty well.
It went through this screw hole.
So, let's put this screw through.
Let's do a temporary fix first.
Quickly and quickly.
Now let's install the fan.
I made it so that it comes out this way.
Here we go.
What?
The screws and screwdriver are magnetically attached.
It's so strong, I'm surprised.
Suddenly I understood.
Okay, the fan is attached.
Next, I'd like to put the motherboard inside the case.
As it is.
Hmmm, it's pretty low.
Oh, this is it.
This is here, right?
These tiny screws, oh, they'll fit.
Oh, wait, this works with a magnet?
Huh!
I'm going to drop it.
So this is how you use it.
Am I right?
That's right.
This is how you grow up.
Maybe?
Yes, I think I could have used 9, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
I think I got all the codes.
Yes, it's okay.
Wow, this is bad.
Let's start from here. I'll start with Catoccio.
Do any of the other members play PC games?
I play with Haruyo Yamaguchi at Playbate.
Also, she said she bought some Naimo.
I think there are about three of us who have gaming PCs, including myself.
I think there are three of us.
But we haven't played with three people yet.
With you?
I've never done it.
I've done it with Haruyo a little.
Well, I think it's going to be a lot of fun. I'm almost done with this.
Well...
This might be a little difficult.
There's a theory that there might be something to this combination.
Wait a minute.
Phew!
This is the hardest quiz I've ever taken.
Are you saying I should put all of these on?
That's right.
Just plug in all the connectors that fit.
I see.
That's good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't do it at this point.
It's right up here.
I said, "This is the right one.
But here are four.
Yes, sir.
That's not fair.
Three needles and four holes.
There are four holes, and this is the right one.
You're right.
Oh? Is this it?
The direction.
Oh, it's facing the other way.
Excuse me.
It's right here, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Is this it?
Wait a minute.
This is terrible.
Crypto-code. Crypto-code.
First of all, power.
Power.
Power
power
north, north, north
it stings!
These four are these little tiny
ug ug ug ug ug
Stabbed.
Is this supposed to be here?
Oh, my God, it floats.
Screws.
It's a screw.
All right.
Surprisingly, this one...
It's on the body.
It says "CPU" or something like that.
It only sticks where it's supposed to stick.
It only goes where it sticks.
Yes, sir.
I'll see what I can do.
I'll try it. Okay.
It's done.
All the cords are connected.
Here it is.
Wow, that's amazing.
The picture shows a lot of wires.
Let's see, this is the bottom.
It looks like this, right?
Here.
Let's plug this in.
Oh, here it is!
I'm sure it's in.
Squeeze!
Squeeze it.
Here you go.
G-Force RTX
Cool!
It's attached!
It doesn't click.
But it's good if it sticks
But it sticks.
Yes, it's stuck.
It's done.
Now, I'd like to turn on the power.
Power on
Power on!
Wow! It's so colorful!
Amazing!
And you can change the color with this LED button!
White is so good!
It's so cool!
You can change it to so many different colors!
The color of the sun is amazing!
I'm going to play a little bit of the game Vallorant!
Okay, let's play Swift!
It's so beautiful, it's so clear, you can even see the jet's eye shadow on the character's eyes!
It's amazing!
I can even see Jet's eye shadow!
It's soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo wet!
It's so beautiful and there's no lag.
You can see the afterimage.
I can see the afterimage.
I wonder if I can beat it with this.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
Nice. Back of the line.
Oh, my God, you got an entry.
You dropped it.
I don't think there's probably anything in there.
Wow, it's beautiful.
All these little names are so beautiful.
The map looks so beautiful.
It's so smooth!
The latest is different.
I knew it was released on that day.
Everything is so easy to play!
Everything is easy to play
It's easy to play.
I feel like I'm already good at it
I feel like I'm so lukewarm, I feel like I'm at my strongest right now
I can't wait to use this at home!
I'm done!
I won!
My first win!
My first win on this first PC.
Ascent!
I knew it was a game I usually play every day.
I was so impressed
I was so impressed by how it changed.
I was also impressed with the game.
I was also impressed by the game and the visuals of the computer.
The visual of this computer is really cool, and it changes a lot of colors.
I'm so excited!
That's all for now, this is Akari's home-built PC project!
Thank you very much!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Please subscribe and rate our channel!
Thank you for watching!